Cristhian Mejias Serrano

cristhianmejias495@gmail.com

y +57 3112262558

🕨 Bogotá, Colombi

Employment

Quality Assurance Manager

Sep 2020 - Feb 2022

Teleperformance, Bogotá

Responsibilities & Tasks:

- Lead Weekly & Monthly Performance Reviews.
- Structure activities distribution for the program.
- Follow up on Quality KPIs and weekly improvement in our Action Plans.
- Develop innovation initiatives like automation & reporting tools.

Quality Assurance Leader

Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

Teleperformance, Bogotá

Responsibilities & Tasks:

- Development of Quality Process in different Lines of Business.
- Creation of Action Plans to improve quality performance.
- Leading Weekly Calibration Sessions with the client
- Participating in Weekly Business Reviews providing insights about the operation performance.
- Managing Quality teams organizing their tasks to comply with Operations requirements.

Quality Assurance Analyst

Oct 2018 - Nov 2019

Teleperformance, Bogotá

Responsibilities & Tasks:

- Perform quality monitoring to customer service calls and emails
- Attend internal and external calibration sessions
- Provide feedback to customer service representatives.
- Lead weekly team meetings to explain the trends and the findings in data.

Education

FullStack Web Development

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

Jan 2022

Digital House

I finished a 6 months long programming bootcamp in order to learn MERN stack and use it to create SPAs.

Psychology Sep 2014 - Jun 2016

Universidad Arturo Michelena, Valencia

Git & GitHub Professional Course

Unconcluded

Courses

Practicing HTML & CSS	Feb 2022
Design for Developers	Feb 2022
Bootstrap	Mar 2022
JavaScript Basics	Mar 2022
Practicing JavaScript	May 2022
JavaScript Data Structures	Jun 2022

Personal details

Website crissmejias.xyz

GitHub

github.com/crissmejias

Profile

My working experience has been more focused in BPO and QA Analytics, however I've been learning Web Development for the last year. I have a special interest in building webs using React & Express.

Skills

JavaScript

React

Nodejs

Express

CSS

Bootstrap

MySQL

Sequelize

APIs

Git

Scrum

MVC Architecture

Excel

Power BI

Languages

Spanish Native

English C1